articleshub.org 2012-09-20

# Articles Hub - Privacy Policy

**General**   
Articleshub places great importance in protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy is designed to explain the manner in which Articleshub collects, uses, and discloses the personal information provided by you as a result of the use of Articleshub's Web Site and the content, information and services provided through the Web Site by Articleshub.

**Users Consent**   
BY ACCESSING THIS WEB SITE, THE WEB SITE LOCATED AT THE URL WWW.ARTICLESHUB.ORG AND/OR ANY OTHER SITE PROVIDED BY Articleshub (COLLECTIVELY, THE "SITE"), YOU ARE SIGNIFYING, EXPRESSING AND PROVIDING YOUR CONSENT TO THE INFORMATION COLLECTION, INFORMATION USAGE, AND OTHER PROCEDURES DESCRIBED IN THE PRIVACY POLICY BELOW. Articleshub reserves the right to change this policy at any time, without notice, by posting a new privacy policy at this location. The collection, use and disclosure of your personal information by Articleshub will be governed by the version of this Policy in effect at that time. Please check this page periodically for any changes. Please [contact us](mailto:webmaster@articleshub.org) if you have any questions about our privacy policy.

**Collection and Use of Information**  
In order for you to access certain materials or pages (i.e. author signup, tell a friend, and the like) and to register as a user on this Site, this Site requires that you provide certain personal information, including, but not limited to, your name, phone number and e-mail address. We use this information in order to contact you to provide you with further information about our company and services, as well as for other commercial and/or internal purposes such as market research in order to better understand the demographics of our Site visitors and potential customers and partners. We may share this information with our authorized partners and/or with third parties who act for or on behalf of us, but we do not otherwise provide or sell any information gathered on this Site to outside vendors.

**Cookies  
**You may have read about "cookies," nuggets of information that are placed by a Web site in a storage place on your own computer. We use cookies to control the display of ads, to track usage patterns on the site, to deliver editorial content, and to record registration and personalization information. For example, if you register on any part of Articles Hub you can opt to save your user name and password on your computer. We can provide this convenience by placing a cookie on your computer. 

Our cookies may contain personally identifiable information and such cookies may be shared with our affiliated companies.

Some of our advertisers occasionally serve you cookies as well. We do not have control over cookies placed by advertisers.

If you don't want cookies, your Web browser likely includes an option that allows you to not accept them. However, if you set your browser to refuse cookies, some portions of Articles Hub may not function properly.

While your individual information is protected as outlined above, we reserve the right to use aggregated anonymous data about our users as a group for any business purpose, such as analyzing usage trends and seeking compatible advertisers and partners. 

**Ip Address  
**Your Internet Protocol ("IP") address is usually associated with the place from which you enter the Internet, like your Internet Service Provider, your company or your university. We may use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, gather broad demographic information, and administer our Web site.

**Hyperlinks**  
This Site contains hyperlinks to other web sites. This privacy policy applies only to this Site and not to any other sites, including sites accessed by hyperlink from this Site. Articleshub has no responsibility, liability for, or control over those other web sites or Internet resources or their collection, use and disclosure of your personal information, nor has it any control over the privacy policies of any of these sites. When you leave the Articleshub.org Site via one of the links then you should read the privacy policy, if any, provided by the site that you have visited.

In order to assist in protecting the confidentiality of your personal information, Articleshub applies security safeguards appropriate to the sensitivity of the information. However, in light of the nature of Internet technologies, security and privacy risks cannot be eliminated and, therefore, Articleshub cannot guarantee that your personal information will not be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Policy.

**3rd Party Based Advertising**

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on Articleshub.org.
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to our site and other sites on the Internet.

You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)
